{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455762076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455762076"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6f2e0346-4dc1-417a-b3a3-e93ce5f7c2fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455764239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455764239"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6f2e0346-4dc1-417a-b3a3-e93ce5f7c2fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455773430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455773429"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455773814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455773813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455774309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455774309"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455774662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455774661"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455775078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455775077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455775561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455775560"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455775791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455775791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455779049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455779049"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455779082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455779082"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455779796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455779795"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455780195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455780195"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455780496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455780495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455780708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455780707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455780909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455780908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455781232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455781232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455781466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455781466"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455784705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455784704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455785116","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455785116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455787714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455787714"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455787926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455787925"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455788137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455788137"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455791646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455791645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455795434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455795433"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455796476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455796475"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455799223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455799222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455799606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455799606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455800100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455800100"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455800452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455800452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455800865","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455800865"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455801347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455801347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455801582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455801582"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455804809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455804809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455804841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455804841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455805555","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455805555"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455805947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455805947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455806241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455806241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455806444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455806444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455806637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455806637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455806950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455806950"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455807173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455807173"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455809903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455809902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455809998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455809998"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455874483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455874483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 802bb46b-7e51-443d-92a5-0e82f1d9287d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455874564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455874564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" c8f90165-a57e-4ada-9c85-452bfde38f13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455888181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455888181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-M-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455892639","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455892639"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_D-O-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455895691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455895691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-T-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455898580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455898580"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-M-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455901676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455901675"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-W-I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455906806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455906806"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_Y-Z-O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455910745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455910744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_M-S-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455914418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455914418"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_L-O-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455918349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455918349"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_M-O-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455921947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455921947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_K-N-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455927726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455927725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 6fd6faf9-841a-4ca9-8da8-d5d454cb80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_O_K-N-O"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455938069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455938068"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455938584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455938584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455939387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455939386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455942246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455942246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455942806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455942806"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455943575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455943574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455946488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455946487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455947061","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455947060"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455947846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455947846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455950962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455950962"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455951224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455951224"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455951934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455951934"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455954782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455954782"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455955292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455955291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455956091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455956091"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455958966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455958965"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455959530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455959529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455960291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455960290"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455963278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455963277"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455963853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455963853"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455964633","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455964632"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455967456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455967455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455967727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455967727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455968521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455968520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455971748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455971747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455971826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455971826"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455982030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455982029"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456016430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456016430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 0e9ba782-65ca-4656-947f-aebafcaa5069"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456016499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456016499"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 8020603e-9f82-441c-895b-66e640498d94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456026328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456026328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456031869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456031869"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456035365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456035365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456039969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456039968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456043140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456043140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456048928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456048928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456052288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456052288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456059952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456059952"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456102998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456102998"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456109521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456109521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456114944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456114944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456123107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456123106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456143520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456143520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456158478","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456158478"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456163587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456163587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456184658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456184658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456193613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456193612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456197766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456197766"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456201186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456201186"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456204904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456204903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456209474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456209474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456244236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456244236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456251663","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456251663"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456255219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456255219"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456259415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456259415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456269794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456269794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456277034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456277034"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456282797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456282796"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 7323846b-3aea-4283-a580-2dda20abbd90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456306825","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456306825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-4-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456311546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456311546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-4-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456316414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456316414"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-8-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456322567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456322567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456327562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456327562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456333016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456333016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456339365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456339365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-1-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456345144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456345144"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-7-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456350650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456350650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456356615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456356614"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-7-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456362607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456362607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456369124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456369122"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 5878db9d-3349-483a-90b7-073a01efd14c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456413202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456413202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 1b93dc53-163f-4abe-8965-b9d2474a64f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456417501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456417500"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 1b93dc53-163f-4abe-8965-b9d2474a64f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456421606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456421605"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 1b93dc53-163f-4abe-8965-b9d2474a64f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456425041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456425041"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 1b93dc53-163f-4abe-8965-b9d2474a64f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456431246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456431245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 1b93dc53-163f-4abe-8965-b9d2474a64f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456435250","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456435249"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 1b93dc53-163f-4abe-8965-b9d2474a64f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456445666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456445665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456446360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456446360"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456447328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456447328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456447528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456447528"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456448128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456448128"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITU"," userResponse":" MWITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456448867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456448867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456449298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456449296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456449888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456449888"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456453495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456453494"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATUMA"," userResponse":" ALIWATUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456454106","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456454106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456454518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456454518"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456455531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456455530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOMESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOMESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456456435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456456435"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456457819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456457818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOTOKA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456458803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456458803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456459395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456459394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456459988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456459988"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456461098","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456461097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456463862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456463862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufaulu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456465298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456465296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufaulu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUFAULU"," userResponse":" HAWAKUFAULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456468573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456468571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijitolea kukomesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456469990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456469990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijitolea kukomesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITOLEA"," userResponse":" ALIJITOLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456471240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456471239"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijitolea kukomesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOMESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOMESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456473893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456473892"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alitumwa nje kuwa mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456474757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456474756"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alitumwa nje kuwa mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMWA"," userResponse":" ALITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456475290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456475289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alitumwa nje kuwa mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456475720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456475720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alitumwa nje kuwa mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456476666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456476665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alitumwa nje kuwa mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456479956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456479956"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456480092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456480091"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456480976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456480976"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANANE"," userResponse":" MANANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456482101","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456482100"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456483026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456483026"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIANZA"," userResponse":" ZILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456483272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456483271"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456483778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456483777"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456484708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456484708"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456485493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456485493"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUA"," userResponse":" KUUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456486170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456486170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku wa manane kelele zilianza na ndovu akaanza kuua vyura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYURA"," userResponse":" VYURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456489122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456489121"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456489702","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456489702"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456490258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456490256"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456491105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456491104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456492449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456492448"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456495536","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456495535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456495765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456495765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456496489","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456496489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUMA"," userResponse":" MAJUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456497402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456497401"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADHAA"," userResponse":" KADHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456498413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456498412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456498957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456498956"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456499879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456499879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456500332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456500332"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456501407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456501406"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456501679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456501678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456502096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456502095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456502972","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456502971"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456504411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456504411"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKOMESHA"," userResponse":" ALIKOMESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456504944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456504944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya majuma kadhaa Mfalme Simba alikuwa mwenye furaha kwa kuwa ndovu alikomesha kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456508409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456508408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456509015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456509015"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456509222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456509222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456510068","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456510067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456511253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456511252"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456511975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456511975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456512695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456512695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456513238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456513237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani mwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAO"," userResponse":" MWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456516365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456516364"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456516903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456516903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456518125","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456518125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456518737","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456518736"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456519609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456519609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAITA"," userResponse":" KUWAITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456520189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456520189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYURA"," userResponse":" VYURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456521232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456521231"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAENDE"," userResponse":" WAENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456521949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456521949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALA"," userResponse":" KUWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456522692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456522691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme Simba alimuuliza ndovu kuwaita vyura waende kuwala wadudu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456525713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456525713"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456526842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456526842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456527119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456527118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456527910","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456527909"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UOGA"," userResponse":" UOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456528440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456528438"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456528964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456528964"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456529966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456529966"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456530699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456530698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEWAUA"," userResponse":" AMEWAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456531373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456531372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu alijawa na uoga kwa vile alikuwa amewaua wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456534592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456534592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456536059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456536058"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAHANI"," userResponse":" SAMAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456537375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456537374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAHANI"," userResponse":" SAMAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456539408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456539408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456539435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456539435"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LI"," userResponse":" LI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456539448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456539448"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUA"," userResponse":" WAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456539999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456539999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456543087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456543087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456543698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456543698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456544229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456544229"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456545073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456545073"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456546572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456546571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456548748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456548747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIKUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456549641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456549641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOMESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOMESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456550146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456550146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456551487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456551487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456552130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456552130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUA"," userResponse":" KUUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456552731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456552730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha Mfalme Simba alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYURA"," userResponse":" VYURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456555098","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456555097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456556109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456556108"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEKWA"," userResponse":" ALIWEKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456557026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456557026"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GEREZANI"," userResponse":" GEREZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456557695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456557694"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456558762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456558762"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndovu aliwekwa gerezani miaka mingi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456562097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456562096"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456563344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456563344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456563943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456563943"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456564485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456564484"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456565621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456565621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFANYE"," userResponse":" WAFANYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456566494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456566493"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456567905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456567904"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILOSEMA"," userResponse":" ALILOSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456569094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456569093"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456569711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456569711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456572752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456572750"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456572836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456572836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 50f156e8-a358-41d1-b0d0-9bcc29b2504b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme aliwaambia wanyama wote wafanye kila alilosema wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456586772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456586772"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456587471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456587471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456588437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456588437"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456588641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456588641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456589245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456589244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITU"," userResponse":" MWITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456589989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456589988"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456590422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456590422"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456591016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456591016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456594556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456594554"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATUMA"," userResponse":" ALIWATUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456595157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456595156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456595565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456595565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456595947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456595947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456596036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456596036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456602396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456602395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 88ec16a3-e19d-4c75-9b62-d3b903ee8904"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwatuma wanyama wake kukomesha kelele zilizotoka kwenye ziwa ndogo mwituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456640686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456640686"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 72f5a06d-58cf-4e38-9647-fb54e1094189"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456658121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456658120"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 72f5a06d-58cf-4e38-9647-fb54e1094189"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456667284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456667284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 72f5a06d-58cf-4e38-9647-fb54e1094189"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456676605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456676605"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 72f5a06d-58cf-4e38-9647-fb54e1094189"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456686067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456686067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 72f5a06d-58cf-4e38-9647-fb54e1094189"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456694806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456694803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 72f5a06d-58cf-4e38-9647-fb54e1094189"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456709141","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456709141"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456718415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456718414"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456720006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456720006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456728652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456728652"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456730269","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456730268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456737741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456737741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456739345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456739345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456746832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456746831"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456748434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456748433"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456755727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456755727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456757329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456757328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456761724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456761724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456763319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456763319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456771687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456771687"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456773266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456773266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456781324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456781324"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456782961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456782961"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456791146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456791146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456792748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456792747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456796013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456796013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456797644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456797644"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456805994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456805994"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456807610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456807610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456814446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456814446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456816034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456816033"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456818754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456818754"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456820766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456820763"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456820893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456820893"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" 844963d2-8af0-4fec-964a-581782887154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456832958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456832957"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456833136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456833136"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456833471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456833470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456834629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456834629"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456835362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456835361"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456838604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456838604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456839248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456839248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456840043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456840043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456840892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456840892"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456841827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456841827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456842518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456842517"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456845485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456845484"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456846210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456846209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456847241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456847240"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456847421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456847421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456848180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456848180"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456851318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456851317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456852136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456852136"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456852203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456852203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456852793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456852792"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456853374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456853374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456854169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456854169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456857633","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456857633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456858267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456858266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456858919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456858919"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456861896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456861896"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456862780","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456862780"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456863881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456863881"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456865053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456865053"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456868409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456868408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456868803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456868802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456869420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456869420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456870637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456870637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456871289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456871288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456872744","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456872744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456873595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456873595"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456876602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456876601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456877588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456877587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456878461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456878460"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456879115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456879115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456880149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456880148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456881440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456881437"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456881483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456881483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456882357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456882357"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456883466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456883465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456885790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456885790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456886546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456886545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456887407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456887407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456889556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456889556"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456890108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456890107"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456890881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456890881"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456891397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456891396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456892192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456892191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456892869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456892869"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456893725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456893725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456896621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456896621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456897422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456897421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456898993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456898993"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456899222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456899222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456899762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456899762"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456900567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456900567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456901186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456901186"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456902241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456902240"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456902743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456902743"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456905182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456905181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456905607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456905606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456906170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456906167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456907537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456907537"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456910993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456910993"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456911922","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456911922"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456912655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456912655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456912884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456912884"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456913477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456913477"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456914332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456914331"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456914518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456914518"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456915140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456915139"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456916987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456916987"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456917760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456917760"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456920753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456920752"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456921575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456921575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456922224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456922224"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456922841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456922841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456923238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456923237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456923442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456923442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456924172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456924172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456927053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456927052"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456927711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456927711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456928549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456928549"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456929254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456929254"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456930051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456930051"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456932641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456932640"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456933840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456933837"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456934629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456934628"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456935416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456935415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456938405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456938405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456940786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456940786"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456940804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456940804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456940838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456940837"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456940849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456940849"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456940855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456940855"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456940871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456940871"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456941736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456941735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456942610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456942610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456945435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456945434"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456945934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456945934"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456946685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456946685"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456947749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456947749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456948163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456948162"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456948880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456948879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456952044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456952044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456952993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456952993"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456953738","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456953737"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456954393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456954392"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456955297","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456955297"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456957997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456957996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456958809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456958809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456959631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456959631"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456962193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456962193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456962813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456962813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456963396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456963396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456964394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456964394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456965295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456965294"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456966349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456966349"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456966928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456966928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456969592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456969592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549456969717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549456969717"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_152225"," gameId":" fc742b69-3eda-4631-836a-721f92488320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}